{
    "id": "ea79ea2f68c54d488287c6ca48d29f09",
    "title": "Confusing pairs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7087ad402a48485daf4366a717613cba",
            "title": "Confusing Pairs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………………. knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "A little",
                        "Little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. children are innocent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Little",
                        "A little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. children are interested in reading.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "A few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has ………………….. buildings of his own.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The …………………. half of the film is more interesting than the former.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "later",
                        "latter"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My …………………. brother works abroad.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Trains run ……………….. five minutes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "every",
                        "each"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… bag is this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Whose",
                        "Who's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog has had ………………….. breakfast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "its",
                        "it's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… is something wrong with this computer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "There",
                        "Their",
                        "There's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}